<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
	<channel>
		<title>Quire &amp; You</title>
		<description>Tips and thoughts to help you achieve your dreams and get things done.</description>		
		<link>https://quire.io</link>
		<atom:link href="https://quire.io/blogfeed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		
			<item>
				<title>How to Use Project Management Software to Measure Employee Productivity</title>
				
					<dc:creator>Quire Marketing Team</dc:creator>
				        
				<description>Project management software can measure employee productivity without micromanaging by being able to easily see which tasks are completed by who and when.</description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 02 Sep 2021 19:58:07 +0800</pubDate>
				<link>https://quire.io/blog/p/measure-productivity.html</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">https://quire.io/blog/p/measure-productivity.html</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>10 Ultimate Tips to Maximize Productivity for Your New Hybrid Work Life</title>
				
					<dc:creator>Quire Marketing Team</dc:creator>
				        
				<description>If you’re looking to maximize productivity in your new hybrid work life, we’ve got 10 tips that can help you both at home and the office.</description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 24 Aug 2021 19:58:07 +0800</pubDate>
				<link>https://quire.io/blog/p/hybrid-work-life-productivity.html</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">https://quire.io/blog/p/hybrid-work-life-productivity.html</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Introducing Quire Subscription Program: Empowering Teams to Dream Bigger</title>
				
					<dc:creator>Vicky Pham</dc:creator>
				        
				<description>Ready to bring your productivity to the next level with Quire? Your favorite software to manage your projects and track the team performance has been upgraded to give you more resources to dream bigger and achieve greater things.</description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 17 Aug 2021 19:58:07 +0800</pubDate>
				<link>https://quire.io/blog/p/pricing.html</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">https://quire.io/blog/p/pricing.html</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Work-Life Balance is so Yesterday, Now We Need Work-Life Integration</title>
				
					<dc:creator>Quire Marketing Team</dc:creator>
				        
				<description>Work-life balance requires trade-offs whereas work-life integration is about finding a harmony between all aspects of daily life. Find out how you can start implementing this today.</description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 10 Aug 2021 19:58:07 +0800</pubDate>
				<link>https://quire.io/blog/p/work-life-integration.html</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">https://quire.io/blog/p/work-life-integration.html</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>No More Unhealthy Overworking Culture; Be Productive Instead</title>
				
					<dc:creator>Quire Marketing Team</dc:creator>
				        
				<description>The culture of overwork is unhealthy as it leads to burnout. The World Health Organization have characterized it as a syndrome, but there is a cure…</description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 03 Aug 2021 19:58:07 +0800</pubDate>
				<link>https://quire.io/blog/p/overtime-working-culture.html</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">https://quire.io/blog/p/overtime-working-culture.html</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Languishing at Work? Here&#39;s How You can Bring Back the Magic to Your Job</title>
				
					<dc:creator>Quire Marketing Team</dc:creator>
				        
				<description>Languishing at work? Here&#39;s how you can bring back the magic to your job with these 7 tips for managing languishing.</description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 27 Jul 2021 19:58:07 +0800</pubDate>
				<link>https://quire.io/blog/p/languishing.html</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">https://quire.io/blog/p/languishing.html</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>The Zeigarnik Effect and How it Affects Productivity</title>
				
					<dc:creator>Quire Marketing Team</dc:creator>
				        
				<description>The Zeigarnik Effect left unchecked will negatively affect productivity and contribute to burnout. In this blog post we look at 5 ways it can be used to book productivity.</description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 13 Jul 2021 19:58:07 +0800</pubDate>
				<link>https://quire.io/blog/p/the-zeigarnik-effect.html</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">https://quire.io/blog/p/the-zeigarnik-effect.html</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>7 Ways to Ensure Employees are Really Working When Working From Home</title>
				
					<dc:creator>Quire Marketing Team</dc:creator>
				        
				<description>In this article we examine 7 ways to ensure your employees are really working when they’re working from home.</description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 29 Jun 2021 19:58:07 +0800</pubDate>
				<link>https://quire.io/blog/p/remote-work.html</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">https://quire.io/blog/p/remote-work.html</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Quire for Microsoft Teams: Collaborate Smarter with Your Teammates</title>
				
					<dc:creator>Vicky Pham</dc:creator>
				        
				<description>Microsoft Teams is a conversation-based collaboration platform that provides chat and cross functional teams with the ability to work together and share information via a common space. This integration with Quire lets users communicate with teammates while directly working on the Quire project.</description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 17 Jun 2021 19:58:07 +0800</pubDate>
				<link>https://quire.io/blog/p/microsoft-teams.html</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">https://quire.io/blog/p/microsoft-teams.html</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Even Zoom CEO has Zoom Fatigue: How to Stop Being Burnout in the Remote Working Era</title>
				
					<dc:creator>Quire Marketing Team</dc:creator>
				        
				<description>Finding that working from home has left you feeling burnt out? Here are 10 thinks you can do to prevent burnout and be more productive and happy.</description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 02 Jun 2021 19:58:07 +0800</pubDate>
				<link>https://quire.io/blog/p/remote-work-burnout.html</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">https://quire.io/blog/p/remote-work-burnout.html</guid>
			</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>
