<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
	<channel>
		<title>Quire &amp; You</title>
		<description>A collaborative task management tool for breaking down goals in hierarchical lists.</description>		
		<link>https://quire.io</link>
		<atom:link href="https://quire.io/blogfeed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		
			<item>
				<title>Never leave your keyboard - Shortcuts that actually make your life easier</title>
				
					<dc:creator>Vicky Pham</dc:creator>
				        
				<description>We would like to reveal some secret shortcuts keys that you might not be aware of on Quire. A full cheatsheet of our unique shortcuts.</description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2019 19:58:07 +0800</pubDate>
				<link>https://quire.io/blog/p/A-few-shortcuts-that-actually-make-your-life-easier.html</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">https://quire.io/blog/p/A-few-shortcuts-that-actually-make-your-life-easier.html</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Quire Mobile 3.0: Kanban Board comes to Mobile App</title>
				
					<dc:creator>Vicky Pham</dc:creator>
				        
				<description>One of the long-awaited features that all of our users have been requesting has come to life. Today we are super excited that we have brought our famous Kanban Board to your Mobile App.</description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2019 19:58:07 +0800</pubDate>
				<link>https://quire.io/blog/p/Quire-Mobile-30-Kanban-Board-Comes-To-Mobile-App.html</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">https://quire.io/blog/p/Quire-Mobile-30-Kanban-Board-Comes-To-Mobile-App.html</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Dream Chasers: How does a Silicon Valley NPO coordinate with 400 volunteers?</title>
				
					<dc:creator>Vicky Pham</dc:creator>
				        
				<description>Realizing that the volunteer project’s scale and complexity have outgrown beyond a regular spreadsheet can track, ZGZG signed up for a Quire account with the hope to find a tool that helps them organize their tasks. They share with us how ZGZG uses Quire to track tasks and boost productivity across their community.</description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2019 19:58:07 +0800</pubDate>
				<link>https://quire.io/blog/p/Dreams-Chasers-How-does-a-Silicon-Valley-NPO-coordinate-with-400-volunteers.html</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">https://quire.io/blog/p/Dreams-Chasers-How-does-a-Silicon-Valley-NPO-coordinate-with-400-volunteers.html</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Dream Chasers: Making a Safer and Cleaner Space Environment</title>
				
					<dc:creator>Vicky Pham</dc:creator>
				        
				<description>Space pollution is indeed a growing problem, but may not be so obvious or visible to people on earth. Alexandre de Villardi de Montlaur and his team are among scientists and engineers trying to solve this problem. Alexandre, coordinator of the most significant project, the ECE3SAT project at ECE Paris, shares with us on how Quire has supported his team in designing a deboriting satellite that seeks to resolve this growing issue.</description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2019 19:58:07 +0800</pubDate>
				<link>https://quire.io/blog/p/Dreams-Chasers-Making-a-Safer-and-Cleaner-Space-Environment.html</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">https://quire.io/blog/p/Dreams-Chasers-Making-a-Safer-and-Cleaner-Space-Environment.html</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Import Your Data From Other Project Management Software</title>
				
					<dc:creator>Vicky Pham</dc:creator>
				        
				<description>Finally, the one feature that everyone is waiting for has become available in Quire. We’re introducing our new import feature in order for all of our users to restore their local backup data or migrate from other project management softwares, including Asana, Trello or Wunderlist.</description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 19 Feb 2019 19:58:07 +0800</pubDate>
				<link>https://quire.io/blog/p/Import-Your-Data-From-Other-Project-Management-Software.html</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">https://quire.io/blog/p/Import-Your-Data-From-Other-Project-Management-Software.html</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Say Hello to Your New Year’s Resolutions in A Productive 2019.</title>
				
					<dc:creator>Crystal Chen</dc:creator>
				        
				<description>We got days till Christmas. And New Year. The moment midnight strikes, people will be making their New Year’s resolutions for 2019. Whether you are starting fresh or picking up projects from where you left off in 2018—we got you covered! Brilliant project starts with brilliant ideas. And it all begins in Quire. You can easily jot down your ideas and organize them...</description>
				<pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 19:58:07 +0800</pubDate>
				<link>https://quire.io/blog/p/Say-Hello-to-Your-New-Year-Resolutions-in-A-Productive-2019.html</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">https://quire.io/blog/p/Say-Hello-to-Your-New-Year-Resolutions-in-A-Productive-2019.html</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>To Do List and Kanban: What Project Management Did Wrong</title>
				
					<dc:creator>Crystal Chen</dc:creator>
				        
				<description>Be it teams, agencies, or companies, there must have been a time when they looked for project management tools or softwares, tried each one of them, and asked all sorts of questions about them, hoping to choose the best project management software to accomplish their next big, amazing projects. Unfortunately, there is no one-for-all, perfect solution. Just the right one to help you boost your productivity...</description>
				<pubDate>Fri, 10 Aug 2018 19:58:07 +0800</pubDate>
				<link>https://quire.io/blog/p/To-Do-List-and-Kanban-What-Project-Management-Did-Wrong.html</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">https://quire.io/blog/p/To-Do-List-and-Kanban-What-Project-Management-Did-Wrong.html</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Quire Mark III: Nested Tasks Meets Board</title>
				
					<dc:creator>Crystal Chen</dc:creator>
				        
				<description>Today, we are proud to announce: Quire Mark III for you to streamline your workflow visually in a board. For years, many Quire users have enjoyed “nested tasks” to see and organize their ideas into a well-planned list of small, actionable to-dos. Now, with Kanban board, execution on your to-dos is made even easier...</description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 23 Jul 2018 19:58:07 +0800</pubDate>
				<link>https://quire.io/blog/p/Quire-Mark-III-Nested-Tasks-Meets-Board.html</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">https://quire.io/blog/p/Quire-Mark-III-Nested-Tasks-Meets-Board.html</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Quire iOS 2.0: New Features and Even Greater Performance</title>
				
					<dc:creator>Crystal Chen</dc:creator>
				        
				<description>Quire is designed to help you realize your goals from first capturing your ideas, to turning them into minimal todos for action. Whenever, wherever you want. Today, we took Quire iOS 2.0 to another level: not only did we added new features, we also enhanced it for better consistency and better UX so you can enjoy the same experience across all devices...</description>
				<pubDate>Fri, 13 Jul 2018 19:58:07 +0800</pubDate>
				<link>https://quire.io/blog/p/Quire-iOS-2.0-New-Features-and-Even-Greater-Performance.html</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">https://quire.io/blog/p/Quire-iOS-2.0-New-Features-and-Even-Greater-Performance.html</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Introducing: New Navigation Bar and Filter</title>
				
					<dc:creator>Crystal Chen</dc:creator>
				        
				<description>Today, we are introducing an upgraded Quire 2.0 to better your navigation, and experience of Quire — we just cannot resist the temptation to perfect our UI/UX! In this upgrade, you will enjoy a new UI for easier, faster navigation between your project’s different views, and a whole new level filtering experience to help you focus on certain tasks...</description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 16 Apr 2018 19:58:07 +0800</pubDate>
				<link>https://quire.io/blog/p/introducing-New-Navigation-Bar-and-Filter.html</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">https://quire.io/blog/p/introducing-New-Navigation-Bar-and-Filter.html</guid>
			</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>
