<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
	<channel>
		<title>Quire &amp; You</title>
		<description>A collaborative task management tool for breaking down goals in hierarchical lists.</description>		
		<link>https://quire.io</link>
		<atom:link href="https://quire.io/blogfeed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		
			<item>
				<title>Quire iOS 2.0: New Features and Even Greater Performance</title>
				
					<dc:creator>Crystal Chen</dc:creator>
				        
				<description>Quire is designed to help you realize your goals from first capturing your ideas, to turning them into minimal todos for action. Whenever, wherever you want. Today, we took Quire iOS 2.0 to another level: not only did we added new features, we also enhanced it for better consistency and better UX so you can enjoy the same experience across all devices...</description>
				<pubDate>Fri, 13 Jul 2018 19:58:07 +0800</pubDate>
				<link>https://quire.io/blog/p/Quire-iOS-2.0-New-Features-and-Even-Greater-Performance.html</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">https://quire.io/blog/p/Quire-iOS-2.0-New-Features-and-Even-Greater-Performance.html</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Introducing: New Navigation Bar and Filter</title>
				
					<dc:creator>Crystal Chen</dc:creator>
				        
				<description>Today, we are introducing an upgraded Quire 2.0 to better your navigation, and experience of Quire — we just cannot resist the temptation to perfect our UI/UX! In this upgrade, you will enjoy a new UI for easier, faster navigation between your project’s different views, and a whole new level filtering experience to help you focus on certain tasks...</description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 16 Apr 2018 19:58:07 +0800</pubDate>
				<link>https://quire.io/blog/p/introducing-New-Navigation-Bar-and-Filter.html</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">https://quire.io/blog/p/introducing-New-Navigation-Bar-and-Filter.html</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Quire: Building a Sophisticated Mobile App with Google’s Flutter</title>
				
					<dc:creator>Jerry Chen</dc:creator>
				        
				<description>A couple years ago, we developed Quire iOS app in Swift. Last year, we chose Flutter for developing Quire Android app. I’d like to share my experience of developing the Android app with Flutter - the good and the bad, the strengths and weaknesses - in this article. I’m a front-end developer of Quire, a simple, lightweight project management tool for capturing ideas, managing tasks and collaborating with teams...</description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 10 Apr 2018 19:58:07 +0800</pubDate>
				<link>https://quire.io/blog/p/Quire-Building-a-Sophisticated-Mobile-App-with-Google-Flutter.html</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">https://quire.io/blog/p/Quire-Building-a-Sophisticated-Mobile-App-with-Google-Flutter.html</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>4 productivity tips that make sense for your project in 2018</title>
				
					<dc:creator>Crystal Chen</dc:creator>
				        
				<description>A new year is a new start, and it often comes with a new determination to do better, and be better. If 2017 ended unhappily for you with chaos like sticky notes being everywhere all the time, figuring out what was where in your head nonstop and chasing after your colleagues for updates tirelessly, it is time for a change....</description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 30 Jan 2018 19:58:07 +0800</pubDate>
				<link>https://quire.io/blog/p/4-productivity-tips-that-make-sense-for-your-project-in-2018.html</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">https://quire.io/blog/p/4-productivity-tips-that-make-sense-for-your-project-in-2018.html</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Introducing: Quire for Android</title>
				
					<dc:creator>Crystal Chen</dc:creator>
				        
				<description>Finally, it is here. Kicking off the new year 2018, we are proud to present to you: Quire for Android. We took time to craft and create this app for Android, so we can get it right. We made sure the layout, navigation, gestures and look-and-feel were simple...</description>
				<pubDate>Fri, 26 Jan 2018 19:58:07 +0800</pubDate>
				<link>https://quire.io/blog/p/Introducing-Quire-for-Android.html</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">https://quire.io/blog/p/Introducing-Quire-for-Android.html</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Highlight Your Tasks with Color and Styles</title>
				
					<dc:creator>Crystal Chen</dc:creator>
				        
				<description>We see it as our mission to keep a simple, clean interface, including a neat task list. However, for those of you who want to easily identify your tasks and projects in a long list, you can use Markdown, and CSS styles to make them stand out...</description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2017 19:58:07 +0800</pubDate>
				<link>https://quire.io/blog/p/Highlight-Your-Tasks-with-Color-and-Styles.html</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">https://quire.io/blog/p/Highlight-Your-Tasks-with-Color-and-Styles.html</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Share a project with your clients, without them sign up!</title>
				
					<dc:creator>Crystal Chen</dc:creator>
				        
				<description>Quire’s “Shared Links” feature makes it super easy for you to collaborate with your clients. We all know that sometimes, clients have their own habits and it is hard to ask them to change. Now, in addition to asking them to sign up Quire, you can get them to view your Quire project with one single invitation link, and zero effort on their part...</description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2017 19:58:07 +0800</pubDate>
				<link>https://quire.io/blog/p/Share-a-project-with-your-clients-without-them-sign-up.html</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">https://quire.io/blog/p/Share-a-project-with-your-clients-without-them-sign-up.html</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Dream Chasers: Taking on the world with the best melons from Brazil</title>
				
					<dc:creator>Crystal Chen</dc:creator>
				        
				<description>José Luís Prado and his family see it as their mission to bring their well-established melons Melão REI from their hometown in Ceará, northern Brazil, to countries all over the globe. Founded in 1983 by his father Carlos, José is the 2nd generation of this family-owned business ITAUEIRA. They grow all kinds of melons from yellow honeydew melons to green melons, watermelons as well as grapes, and ship them to countries...</description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2017 19:58:07 +0800</pubDate>
				<link>https://quire.io/blog/p/Dream-Chasers-Taking-on-the-world-with-the-best-melons-from-Brazil.html</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">https://quire.io/blog/p/Dream-Chasers-Taking-on-the-world-with-the-best-melons-from-Brazil.html</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Quire + Siri: Add tasks with your voice for iOS 11</title>
				
					<dc:creator>Crystal Chen</dc:creator>
				        
				<description>Your smart assistant Siri just got smarter with iOS 11 for you in Quire. Just like in our earlier blog post, simply call up Siri and tell her/him the task, the assignee and a due date and time, and it will be added directly to Quire. No need to open the app, or unlock your phone! And now with iOS 11, the conversation has become even more natural...</description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 13 Nov 2017 19:58:07 +0800</pubDate>
				<link>https://quire.io/blog/p/Quire-Siri-Add-tasks-with-your-voice-for-iOS-11.html</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">https://quire.io/blog/p/Quire-Siri-Add-tasks-with-your-voice-for-iOS-11.html</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Quire and Slack work great together.</title>
				
					<dc:creator>Crystal Chen</dc:creator>
				        
				<description>It is our mission to help you work seamlessly via Quire and other apps you are already comfortably using. With the integration with Slack, we are one step closer. For those of you who often communicate on Slack, you and your team can now receive updates about your Quire projects...</description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2017 19:58:07 +0800</pubDate>
				<link>https://quire.io/blog/p/Quire-and-Slack-work-great-together.html</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">https://quire.io/blog/p/Quire-and-Slack-work-great-together.html</guid>
			</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>
