<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
	<channel>
		<title>Quire &amp; You</title>
		<description>A collaborative task management tool for breaking down goals in hierarchical lists.</description>		
		<link>https://quire.io</link>
		<atom:link href="https://quire.io/blogfeed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		
			<item>
				<title>3 Proven Tips on How to Run Effective Meetings with a Digital To Do List</title>
				
					<dc:creator>Vicky Pham</dc:creator>
				        
				<description>It’s time to stop the meeting madness and seek for improvement from another angle: using a digital to do list app as a tool to combat with meetings instead of the traditional approach.</description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2019 19:58:07 +0800</pubDate>
				<link>https://quire.io/blog/p/3-proven-tips-on-how-to-run-effective-meetings-with-a-digital-to-do-list.html</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">https://quire.io/blog/p/3-proven-tips-on-how-to-run-effective-meetings-with-a-digital-to-do-list.html</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>7 Productivity Tips to Avoid Burnout at Work</title>
				
					<dc:creator>Vicky Pham</dc:creator>
				        
				<description>No one wants to be unhappy at work. When realizing some burnout symptoms,  you can start making some adjustments to the way you’re doing your job. Here are some proven effective tips to avoid burnout and get your smile back.</description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2019 19:58:07 +0800</pubDate>
				<link>https://quire.io/blog/p/7-productivity-tips-to-avoid-burnout-at-work.html</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">https://quire.io/blog/p/7-productivity-tips-to-avoid-burnout-at-work.html</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Set Up GTD Method in Quire to Live a Stress-free Life</title>
				
					<dc:creator>Vicky Pham</dc:creator>
				        
				<description>The GTD method is a way to organize, categorize, plan and execute your tasks. Many people discussed and argued whether GTD methodology is really efficient given its complexity. However, as straightforward as it is, GTD is set up to help you answer one question “When to do what?”. In this post, we&#39;re going to introduce how to set up GTD Method in Quire for you to live a stress-free life.</description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2019 19:58:07 +0800</pubDate>
				<link>https://quire.io/blog/p/Setup-GTD-Method-in-Quire.html</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">https://quire.io/blog/p/Setup-GTD-Method-in-Quire.html</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Quire Peekaboo and GTD Methodology: A Miracle for Your Productivity Hack</title>
				
					<dc:creator>Vicky Pham</dc:creator>
				        
				<description>Researchers have pointed out that incomplete tasks can trigger stress - especially at workplace. Trying to combat with an overwhelming list with thousands of unfinished to-dos can drain energy, make you lose motivation and get tired easily. Sometimes, listing out everything you need to do does more harm than good. Rather than trying to be an overachieving superhero, how about just be an ordinary person with an effective working method?</description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2019 19:58:07 +0800</pubDate>
				<link>https://quire.io/blog/p/Quire-Peekaboo-and-GTD-Methodology.html</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">https://quire.io/blog/p/Quire-Peekaboo-and-GTD-Methodology.html</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Top 3 Productivity Tips With Online To Do List Software</title>
				
					<dc:creator>Vicky Pham</dc:creator>
				        
				<description>In a fiercely competitive digital landscape, great project management is a vital skill for teams and individuals alike. Disorganization and inefficiency can devastate the most promising teams and projects. There is certainly no shortage of project management tools offering solutions to this challenge. One such grouping of tools is generally referred to as online to do list software...</description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2019 19:58:07 +0800</pubDate>
				<link>https://quire.io/blog/p/Top-3-Online-To-Do-List-Software-Productivity-Tips.html</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">https://quire.io/blog/p/Top-3-Online-To-Do-List-Software-Productivity-Tips.html</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Creating Quire Desktop App from Google Chrome</title>
				
					<dc:creator>Vicky Pham</dc:creator>
				        
				<description>Right now Quire only has a web browser version and a native iOS and Android app, a lot of our users have requested a native MacOs and Windows desktop app. While our developers are working on making the desktop app happen (not soon, unfortunately), there’s a simple way to let you create an app with Google Chrome.</description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2019 19:58:07 +0800</pubDate>
				<link>https://quire.io/blog/p/Creating-Quire-Desktop-App-from-Chrome.html</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">https://quire.io/blog/p/Creating-Quire-Desktop-App-from-Chrome.html</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Never leave your keyboard - Shortcuts that actually make your life easier</title>
				
					<dc:creator>Vicky Pham</dc:creator>
				        
				<description>You’re always busy with your work, we know that. You don&#39;t like to go back and forth between keyboard and mouse since it&#39;s just a waste of time? No worries, we&#39;ve got you covered. Now with our full set of shortcut keys, you can do most of the actions with your keyboard, don’t have to reach to your mouse to edit Quire workspace anymore.</description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2019 19:58:07 +0800</pubDate>
				<link>https://quire.io/blog/p/A-few-shortcuts-that-actually-make-your-life-easier.html</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">https://quire.io/blog/p/A-few-shortcuts-that-actually-make-your-life-easier.html</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Quire Mobile 3.0: Kanban Board comes to Mobile App</title>
				
					<dc:creator>Vicky Pham</dc:creator>
				        
				<description>One of the long-awaited features that all of our users have been requesting has come to life. Today we are super excited that we have brought our famous Kanban Board to your Mobile App.</description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2019 19:58:07 +0800</pubDate>
				<link>https://quire.io/blog/p/Quire-Mobile-30-Kanban-Board-Comes-To-Mobile-App.html</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">https://quire.io/blog/p/Quire-Mobile-30-Kanban-Board-Comes-To-Mobile-App.html</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Dream Chasers: How does a Silicon Valley NPO coordinate with 400 volunteers?</title>
				
					<dc:creator>Vicky Pham</dc:creator>
				        
				<description>Realizing that the volunteer project’s scale and complexity have outgrown beyond a regular spreadsheet can track, ZGZG signed up for a Quire account with the hope to find a tool that helps them organize their tasks. They share with us how ZGZG uses Quire to track tasks and boost productivity across their community.</description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2019 19:58:07 +0800</pubDate>
				<link>https://quire.io/blog/p/Dreams-Chasers-How-does-a-Silicon-Valley-NPO-coordinate-with-400-volunteers.html</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">https://quire.io/blog/p/Dreams-Chasers-How-does-a-Silicon-Valley-NPO-coordinate-with-400-volunteers.html</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Dream Chasers: Making a Safer and Cleaner Space Environment</title>
				
					<dc:creator>Vicky Pham</dc:creator>
				        
				<description>Space pollution is indeed a growing problem, but may not be so obvious or visible to people on earth. Alexandre de Villardi de Montlaur and his team are among scientists and engineers trying to solve this problem. Alexandre, coordinator of the most significant project, the ECE3SAT project at ECE Paris, shares with us on how Quire has supported his team in designing a deboriting satellite that seeks to resolve this growing issue.</description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2019 19:58:07 +0800</pubDate>
				<link>https://quire.io/blog/p/Dreams-Chasers-Making-a-Safer-and-Cleaner-Space-Environment.html</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">https://quire.io/blog/p/Dreams-Chasers-Making-a-Safer-and-Cleaner-Space-Environment.html</guid>
			</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>
