<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
	<channel>
		<title>Quire &amp; You</title>
		<description>Tips and thoughts to help you achieve your dreams and get things done.</description>		
		<link>https://quire.io</link>
		<atom:link href="https://quire.io/blogfeed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		
			<item>
				<title>Introducing Quire Mobile 5.0 and Everything You Need to Know</title>
				
					<dc:creator>Vicky Pham</dc:creator>
				        
				<description>We can’t be more excited to introduce you with Quire Mobile 5.0 - a brand new chapter for both Quire iOS and Android users! Faster performance, more user-focused interface, all-new tabbed navigation, dynamic search, new feature Sublist, etc., basically everything gets better with the all-new design Quire Mobile 5.0.</description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 09 Apr 2020 19:58:07 +0800</pubDate>
				<link>https://quire.io/blog/p/introducing-new-mobile-app.html</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">https://quire.io/blog/p/introducing-new-mobile-app.html</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Coronavirus Outbreak: How to Work From Home and Still Stay Productive</title>
				
					<dc:creator>Vicky Pham</dc:creator>
				        
				<description>Social distancing is implemented to slow down the spread of Coronavirus. Don&#39;t freak out if it&#39;s your first work-at-home experience, we will tell you the ultimate guides, from setting up your new office to the way you collaborate with your team from afar.</description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 25 Mar 2020 19:58:07 +0800</pubDate>
				<link>https://quire.io/blog/p/work-from-home-tips.html</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">https://quire.io/blog/p/work-from-home-tips.html</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Quire joins forces with Google and Zoom to offer free accounts for Nonprofits</title>
				
					<dc:creator>Vicky Pham</dc:creator>
				        
				<description>We understand your struggles, and we would like to share the burden with all of the Nonprofits who have been suffering financially amid the coronavirus pandemic. Quire will offer completely free accounts for Nonprofits during the outbreak, no strings attached.</description>
				<pubDate>Fri, 20 Mar 2020 19:58:07 +0800</pubDate>
				<link>https://quire.io/blog/p/coronavirus-nonprofits-free-accounts.html</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">https://quire.io/blog/p/coronavirus-nonprofits-free-accounts.html</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>The Ultimate Guide to Kanban Swimlanes for Better Project Management</title>
				
					<dc:creator>Vicky Pham</dc:creator>
				        
				<description>Kanban board is proven to play a critical role in project management. One of the most important practices of Kanban Board is the Swimlane. This ultimate guide will tell you what Kanban Swimlane is and how to become a Kanban expert.</description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 17 Mar 2020 19:58:07 +0800</pubDate>
				<link>https://quire.io/blog/p/Kanban-board-swimlane.html</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">https://quire.io/blog/p/Kanban-board-swimlane.html</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Best 5 tips to Use a Digital To Do List for Remote Teams during a Virus Outbreak</title>
				
					<dc:creator>Vicky Pham</dc:creator>
				        
				<description>Building a global remote team during the outbreak can take a village, but talented people from across the world can still successfully collaborate as long as leaders can choose the best platform for the team to thrive.</description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 05 Mar 2020 19:58:07 +0800</pubDate>
				<link>https://quire.io/blog/p/to-do-list-tips-remote-teams.html</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">https://quire.io/blog/p/to-do-list-tips-remote-teams.html</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Top 12 Quire Hacks that Make Your Productivity Great Again</title>
				
					<dc:creator>Vicky Pham</dc:creator>
				        
				<description>Team productivity can slow down a bit with all of the cluttered task list, messy organization and awkward communication. In the spirit of sharing, in this post, we will let you know some of the top-notch Quire tips and hacks to make your productivity in 2020 great again!</description>
				<pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2020 19:58:07 +0800</pubDate>
				<link>https://quire.io/blog/p/Quire-tips-hacks-for-better-productivity.html</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">https://quire.io/blog/p/Quire-tips-hacks-for-better-productivity.html</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Quire Sublist: Bridge the Gap between Team To Do Lists and Personal Productivity</title>
				
					<dc:creator>Vicky Pham</dc:creator>
				        
				<description>At Quire, we never let the stress win and make you feel less of yourself. It&#39;s not you, it’s the way your team works with the to do list. Today, in order to solve the frustration and distraction problems once and for all, we introduce you with the ultimate Quire Sublist - the feature that will change the way you deal with your task list forever.</description>
				<pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2020 19:58:07 +0800</pubDate>
				<link>https://quire.io/blog/p/Quire-sublist.html</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">https://quire.io/blog/p/Quire-sublist.html</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Best New Year&#39;s Resolutions that You Can Actually Keep in 2020</title>
				
					<dc:creator>Vicky Pham</dc:creator>
				        
				<description>We want to kickstart a decade with a clean slate. Instead of keep making general resolutions as “losing weight” or “saving up”, we will tell you some awesome easy New Year’s resolutions that are not too difficult to keep for you to be more productive in 2020.</description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2019 19:58:07 +0800</pubDate>
				<link>https://quire.io/blog/p/best-new-year-resolutions-to-keep.html</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">https://quire.io/blog/p/best-new-year-resolutions-to-keep.html</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>What a year it’s been: Looking back at the incredible journey with Quire in 2019</title>
				
					<dc:creator>Vicky Pham</dc:creator>
				        
				<description>Christmas is rolling around and soon we will be making toasts celebrating another promising 365 days. By all accounts, 2019 has been a remarkable year for us at Quire and we would like to take a moment and share with you the incredible journey of the last 12 months.</description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2019 19:58:07 +0800</pubDate>
				<link>https://quire.io/blog/p/look-back-at-2019.html</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">https://quire.io/blog/p/look-back-at-2019.html</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Meet Quire Team: Our Favorite Productivity Things in 2019</title>
				
					<dc:creator>Vicky Pham</dc:creator>
				        
				<description>There are thousands of books, videos and blog posts available everywhere to teach you how to get more productive. The problem is, those pieces of advice can get very cliche and most of the time, you will forget everything you’ve just read in just 10 minutes, let alone follow the tips to improve your productivity. As a team who specializes in creating a tool to help everyone with workload efficiency, Quire team has put together a list of our favorites to keep a healthy work-life balance and help you improve your productivity in 2020!</description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2019 19:58:07 +0800</pubDate>
				<link>https://quire.io/blog/p/Quire-favorite-productivity-things.html</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">https://quire.io/blog/p/Quire-favorite-productivity-things.html</guid>
			</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>
