<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
	<channel>
		<title>Quire &amp; You</title>
		<description>Tips and thoughts to help you achieve your dreams and get things done.</description>		
		<link>https://quire.io</link>
		<atom:link href="https://quire.io/blogfeed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		
			<item>
				<title>7 Productivity Rituals to Work Better Under Time Pressure</title>
				
					<dc:creator>Josh Guilar</dc:creator>
				        
				<description>In this blog post we look at 7 productivity rituals that will help you work better and more efficiently with time pressure.</description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 02 Dec 2020 19:58:07 +0800</pubDate>
				<link>https://quire.io/blog/p/productivity-ritual.html</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">https://quire.io/blog/p/productivity-ritual.html</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>15 Productivity Tips from Bill Gates, Elon Musk, Warren Buffet and Others</title>
				
					<dc:creator>Josh Guilar</dc:creator>
				        
				<description>Want to know how some of the most successful entrepreneurs maintain their success? Here are 15 productivity tips from some of the most successful entrepreneurs of all time.</description>
				<pubDate>Fri, 27 Nov 2020 19:58:07 +0800</pubDate>
				<link>https://quire.io/blog/p/productivity-advice-from-enterpreneurs.html</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">https://quire.io/blog/p/productivity-advice-from-enterpreneurs.html</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Sharing is Caring - You are All Invited to Join #QuireGivesBack Giveaway</title>
				
					<dc:creator>Vicky Pham</dc:creator>
				        
				<description>Enter to win Amazon US$100 gift card, Premium Quire subscription, limited Quire goodies and other awesome prize packs.</description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 17 Nov 2020 19:58:07 +0800</pubDate>
				<link>https://quire.io/blog/p/giveaway.html</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">https://quire.io/blog/p/giveaway.html</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>10 Key Benefits of Using a Work Management Software for Remote Teams</title>
				
					<dc:creator>Josh Guilar</dc:creator>
				        
				<description>Using work management software for remote teams is the easiest way to ensure all of your projects are carried out on time and to the client’s specifications.</description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 12 Nov 2020 19:58:07 +0800</pubDate>
				<link>https://quire.io/blog/p/work-management-tips.html</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">https://quire.io/blog/p/work-management-tips.html</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>What is Work Management Software and Why Your Team Needs One</title>
				
					<dc:creator>Josh Guilar</dc:creator>
				        
				<description>A project management platform is great for managing projects. But if you want to better manage your organization, your projects and your team, then a work management platform is the ideal solution.</description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 03 Nov 2020 19:58:07 +0800</pubDate>
				<link>https://quire.io/blog/p/work-management-software.html</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">https://quire.io/blog/p/work-management-software.html</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>10 Tips for Transforming Into a High Performing Agile Team</title>
				
					<dc:creator>Josh Guilar</dc:creator>
				        
				<description>Agile teams, like any, face their challenges. And while the agile method has often been discussed like a magic cure-all for organization and task efficiency, it’s got to be done properly in order to be successful.</description>
				<pubDate>Fri, 23 Oct 2020 19:58:07 +0800</pubDate>
				<link>https://quire.io/blog/p/agile-team-tips.html</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">https://quire.io/blog/p/agile-team-tips.html</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Deprecating Support For Internet Explorer Browser Starting From 2021</title>
				
					<dc:creator>Vicky Pham</dc:creator>
				        
				<description>Today, we are sorry to say that Quire will no longer support Internet Explorer (IE) by December 31, 2020. This means, starting from 2021, if you’re using IE, you cannot load or view Quire’s workspace anymore.</description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 21 Oct 2020 19:58:07 +0800</pubDate>
				<link>https://quire.io/blog/p/internet-explorer-deprecating.html</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">https://quire.io/blog/p/internet-explorer-deprecating.html</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>&#39;Okay Google, talk to Quire!&#39;</title>
				
					<dc:creator>Vicky Pham</dc:creator>
				        
				<description>Connect Quire with Google Assistant - the voice-controlled virtual assistant powered by Google. Manage your task list without having to open Quire app.</description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 20 Oct 2020 19:58:07 +0800</pubDate>
				<link>https://quire.io/blog/p/google-assistant.html</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">https://quire.io/blog/p/google-assistant.html</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>What is Agile Project Management and How Remote Teams Implement Agile With a Team Management Software</title>
				
					<dc:creator>Josh Guilar</dc:creator>
				        
				<description>Agile project management is about being agile and adapting to what’s in front of you. For remote teams this is most effectively achieved by using team management software.</description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 19:58:07 +0800</pubDate>
				<link>https://quire.io/blog/p/agile-project-management.html</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">https://quire.io/blog/p/agile-project-management.html</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Achieve Stress-Free Productivity with Quire and Email Integrations</title>
				
					<dc:creator>Vicky Pham</dc:creator>
				        
				<description>Achieve highest productivity level with Quire! Turn your emails into tasks or get instant notifications in your mailbox with the click of a button and you will be set to focus on actually getting things done!</description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 30 Sep 2020 19:58:07 +0800</pubDate>
				<link>https://quire.io/blog/p/email-integrations%20copy.html</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">https://quire.io/blog/p/email-integrations%20copy.html</guid>
			</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>
