<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
	<channel>
		<title>Quire &amp; You</title>
		<description>A collaborative task management tool for breaking down goals in hierarchical lists.</description>		
		<link>https://quire.io</link>
		<atom:link href="https://quire.io/blogfeed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		
			<item>
				<title>Quire My Tasks II: Redesign the way you kickstart a day</title>
				
					<dc:creator>Vicky Pham</dc:creator>
				        
				<description>Drum roll please! Today we’re thrilled to introduce you with the brand-new renovated My Tasks II. Now you can have your own Quire to-do list to keep track of all the tasks that are related to you. My Tasks is a default task list in Quire. Before, you have to select a project before adding a task. However, with the newly redesigned My Tasks, you can directly add a task to Quire without being specific about the project.</description>
				<pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 19:58:07 +0800</pubDate>
				<link>https://quire.io/blog/p/Introduce-Quire-New-My-Tasks.html</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">https://quire.io/blog/p/Introduce-Quire-New-My-Tasks.html</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Quire - Behind the Scenes: The Untold Stories</title>
				
					<dc:creator>Vicky Pham</dc:creator>
				        
				<description>Unwilling to settle for all the complexity, Quire was born as an answer to conquering a big project and achieving your dreams. Maybe you’re new to Quire or you’ve been a Quirean for a long time, we would like to share with you the journey of Quire. Today we’re thrilled to bring you an interview with Tom - the creator of Quire.  As a serial entrepreneur and a software developer, Tom shares with us his insightful tips to deal with software complexity, how to boost team productivity, and more!</description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 21 Oct 2019 19:58:07 +0800</pubDate>
				<link>https://quire.io/blog/p/Quire-behind-the-scenes-productivity-tips.html</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">https://quire.io/blog/p/Quire-behind-the-scenes-productivity-tips.html</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Dream Chasers: Start Your Dreams on Mars</title>
				
					<dc:creator>Vicky Pham</dc:creator>
				        
				<description>Exploring Mars is no longer just a wild dream to human beings anymore. Team Tumbleweed is a group of currently 16 students that is building a wind-driven Mars rover. The team is located at TU Delft in the Netherlands, TU Wien in Austria, and at Stanford University in the US.</description>
				<pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2019 19:58:07 +0800</pubDate>
				<link>https://quire.io/blog/p/Dreams-Chasers-Start-your-dreams-on-Mars.html</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">https://quire.io/blog/p/Dreams-Chasers-Start-your-dreams-on-Mars.html</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Be a Hero: Create Your Own App with Quire API</title>
				
					<dc:creator>Jimmy Shiau</dc:creator>
				        
				<description>We are happy to announce the release of version 1.0.0 of our OpenAPI, Quire uses OAuth 2.0 to authenticate requests between your app and your users. With OAuth, users can give you access to their Quire content without giving up their passwords.</description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2019 19:58:07 +0800</pubDate>
				<link>https://quire.io/blog/p/Create-Your-Quire-App-with-Quire-API.html</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">https://quire.io/blog/p/Create-Your-Quire-App-with-Quire-API.html</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Quire &amp; Beyond: Build great things with Quire API</title>
				
					<dc:creator>Vicky Pham</dc:creator>
				        
				<description>Today, we’re very excited to announce that Quire API is officially available for all of you to start building great things with Quire. Quire API lets you build scripts and integrate your favorite applications with Quire. You can choose to share your application with your organization members only or you can let other users in Quire community enjoy your application by publishing it in Quire App Directory.</description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2019 19:58:07 +0800</pubDate>
				<link>https://quire.io/blog/p/Quire-and-Beyond-Announce-Quire-API.html</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">https://quire.io/blog/p/Quire-and-Beyond-Announce-Quire-API.html</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>8 Best Tips for Remote Teams to Boost Productivity at Virtual Office</title>
				
					<dc:creator>Vicky Pham</dc:creator>
				        
				<description>We are living in a fast-paced society where everything needs to be done quickly without any hassles. Nothing kills joy and productivity more than being chained to a desk for 8 hours a day and 5 days a week. Employees are happier when they can choose to work from home or at a rustic coffee shop, no matter if they are night owls or early birds, they have different options to make the schedule work best for their creativity and productivity.</description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2019 19:58:07 +0800</pubDate>
				<link>https://quire.io/blog/p/8-best-tips-for-remote-teams-to-boost-productivity-at-virtual-office.html</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">https://quire.io/blog/p/8-best-tips-for-remote-teams-to-boost-productivity-at-virtual-office.html</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Busy vs. Productive: 5 Tips to Improve Time Management Skills for Project Managers</title>
				
					<dc:creator>Vicky Pham</dc:creator>
				        
				<description>Why are you always busy but not productive? We&#39;re more than halfway through 2019 and it&#39;s about time to stop living like a zoombie because you are behind most of your deadlines. With our 5 simple tips to improve time management skills, you can own your day, become less busy and more productive.</description>
				<pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2019 19:58:07 +0800</pubDate>
				<link>https://quire.io/blog/p/5-tips-to-improve-time-management-skills.html</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">https://quire.io/blog/p/5-tips-to-improve-time-management-skills.html</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>3 Proven Tips on How to Run Effective Meetings with a Digital To Do List</title>
				
					<dc:creator>Vicky Pham</dc:creator>
				        
				<description>It’s time to stop the meeting madness and seek for improvement from another angle: use a digital to do list app as a tool to combat dreadful meetings instead of the traditional approach.</description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2019 19:58:07 +0800</pubDate>
				<link>https://quire.io/blog/p/3-proven-tips-on-how-to-run-effective-meetings-with-a-digital-to-do-list.html</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">https://quire.io/blog/p/3-proven-tips-on-how-to-run-effective-meetings-with-a-digital-to-do-list.html</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>7 Productivity Tips to Avoid Burnout at Work</title>
				
					<dc:creator>Vicky Pham</dc:creator>
				        
				<description>No one wants to be unhappy at work. When realizing some burnout symptoms,  you can start making some adjustments to the way you’re doing your job. Here are some proven effective tips to avoid burnout and get your smile back.</description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2019 19:58:07 +0800</pubDate>
				<link>https://quire.io/blog/p/7-productivity-tips-to-avoid-burnout-at-work.html</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">https://quire.io/blog/p/7-productivity-tips-to-avoid-burnout-at-work.html</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Set Up GTD Method in Quire to Live a Stress-free Life</title>
				
					<dc:creator>Vicky Pham</dc:creator>
				        
				<description>The GTD method is a way to organize, categorize, plan and execute your tasks. Many people discussed and argued whether GTD methodology is really efficient given its complexity. However, as straightforward as it is, GTD is set up to help you answer one question “When to do what?”. In this post, we&#39;re going to introduce how to set up GTD Method in Quire for you to live a stress-free life.</description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2019 19:58:07 +0800</pubDate>
				<link>https://quire.io/blog/p/Setup-GTD-Method-in-Quire.html</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">https://quire.io/blog/p/Setup-GTD-Method-in-Quire.html</guid>
			</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>
