<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
	<channel>
		<title>Quire &amp; You</title>
		<description>Tips and thoughts to help you achieve your dreams and get things done.</description>		
		<link>https://quire.io</link>
		<atom:link href="https://quire.io/blogfeed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		
			<item>
				<title>How to Boost Teamwork Performance with Transparent Communication</title>
				
					<dc:creator>Josh Guilar</dc:creator>
				        
				<description>Transparency is an important part of team communication, and how a task management software like Quire can help.</description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 04 Aug 2020 19:58:07 +0800</pubDate>
				<link>https://quire.io/blog/p/transparency-in-communication.html</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">https://quire.io/blog/p/transparency-in-communication.html</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>How a Task Management Software Helps Businesses Achieve Higher Productivity in a Post-pandemic World</title>
				
					<dc:creator>Josh Guilar</dc:creator>
				        
				<description>How a task management software (Quire) helps online businesses achieve higher productivity in a post-pandemic world.</description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 14 Jul 2020 19:58:07 +0800</pubDate>
				<link>https://quire.io/blog/p/task-management-software-helps-productivity.html</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">https://quire.io/blog/p/task-management-software-helps-productivity.html</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Zapier Meets Quire: Automate the Way You Work</title>
				
					<dc:creator>Vicky Pham</dc:creator>
				        
				<description>Zapier was born to instantly connect thousands of apps so they can work together and ultimately help users simplify their workflows. Integrate Zapier to your Quire projects to optimize the way you work.</description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 07 Jul 2020 19:58:07 +0800</pubDate>
				<link>https://quire.io/blog/p/zapier-integration.html</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">https://quire.io/blog/p/zapier-integration.html</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>How to Use Apple Sign-in with Quire</title>
				
					<dc:creator>Vicky Pham</dc:creator>
				        
				<description>Sign in with Apple makes it easy for users to access Quire using Touch ID, Face ID and device passcode. Turn on and set up Apple Sign-in to start working on your projects with Quire!</description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 24 Jun 2020 19:58:07 +0800</pubDate>
				<link>https://quire.io/blog/p/apple-sign-in.html</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">https://quire.io/blog/p/apple-sign-in.html</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>A Guide to Deep Work: How to Achieve the Ultimate Productivity</title>
				
					<dc:creator>Josh Guilar</dc:creator>
				        
				<description>If you are looking to achieve the ultimate productivity with Deep Work, we have put together this helpful guide that answers all your questions.</description>
				<pubDate>Fri, 12 Jun 2020 19:58:07 +0800</pubDate>
				<link>https://quire.io/blog/p/how-to-deep-work.html</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">https://quire.io/blog/p/how-to-deep-work.html</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>How to Take a Break When Working Remotely to Increase Productivity?</title>
				
					<dc:creator>Vicky Pham</dc:creator>
				        
				<description>We are obsessed with being “work martyrs” to prove our abilities to meet deadlines and complete the to-do lists every single day. Don&#39;t let your job take away your happiness! Here are some tips for you to take a break when working remotely and still get things done!</description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 27 May 2020 19:58:07 +0800</pubDate>
				<link>https://quire.io/blog/p/how-to-properly-take-a-break.html</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">https://quire.io/blog/p/how-to-properly-take-a-break.html</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>6 Mistakes Project Managers Make that Kill Productivity</title>
				
					<dc:creator>Josh Guilar</dc:creator>
				        
				<description>In this article, Quire looks at 6 mistakes project managers make that kill productivity and what you can do to avoid them.</description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 18 May 2020 19:58:07 +0800</pubDate>
				<link>https://quire.io/blog/p/productivity-mistakes.html</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">https://quire.io/blog/p/productivity-mistakes.html</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>The Art of Being Productive While Staying In</title>
				
					<dc:creator>Vicky Pham</dc:creator>
				        
				<description>As social distancing and self quarantining continue, here are some effective tips to keep you sane during lockdown and still being productive. Being a remote team, we have put together some of the best life hacks for you to enjoy the solitude during this unprecedented time.</description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 05 May 2020 19:58:07 +0800</pubDate>
				<link>https://quire.io/blog/p/productivity-tips-during-lockdown.html</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">https://quire.io/blog/p/productivity-tips-during-lockdown.html</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Wunderlist Alternative: Effortlessly Switch to Quire</title>
				
					<dc:creator>Vicky Pham</dc:creator>
				        
				<description>Effortlessly migrate your tasks, to-do lists, folders, projects from Wunderlist to Quire. Change is frustrating, but we made it easy for you! No more looking for the best Wunderlist alternative. Welcome to a task management software that is here to stay!</description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 29 Apr 2020 19:58:07 +0800</pubDate>
				<link>https://quire.io/blog/p/wunderlist-alternatives.html</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">https://quire.io/blog/p/wunderlist-alternatives.html</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Introducing Quire Mobile 5.0 and Everything You Need to Know</title>
				
					<dc:creator>Vicky Pham</dc:creator>
				        
				<description>We can’t be more excited to introduce you with Quire Mobile 5.0 - a brand new chapter for both Quire iOS and Android users! Faster performance, more user-focused interface, all-new tabbed navigation, dynamic search, new feature Sublist, etc., basically everything gets better with the all-new design Quire Mobile 5.0.</description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 11 Apr 2020 19:58:07 +0800</pubDate>
				<link>https://quire.io/blog/p/introducing-new-mobile-app.html</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">https://quire.io/blog/p/introducing-new-mobile-app.html</guid>
			</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>
