<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
	<channel>
		<title>Quire &amp; You</title>
		<description>Tips and thoughts to help you achieve your dreams and get things done.</description>		
		<link>https://quire.io</link>
		<atom:link href="https://quire.io/blogfeed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		
			<item>
				<title>How to Use Apple Sign-in with Quire</title>
				
					<dc:creator>Vicky Pham</dc:creator>
				        
				<description>Sign in with Apple makes it easy for users to access Quire using Touch ID, Face ID and device passcode. Turn on and set up Apple Sign-in to start working on your projects with Quire!</description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 24 Jun 2020 19:58:07 +0800</pubDate>
				<link>https://quire.io/blog/p/apple-sign-in.html</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">https://quire.io/blog/p/apple-sign-in.html</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>A Guide to Deep Work: How to Achieve the Ultimate Productivity</title>
				
					<dc:creator>Josh Guilar</dc:creator>
				        
				<description>If you are looking to achieve the ultimate productivity with Deep Work, we have put together this helpful guide that answers all your questions.</description>
				<pubDate>Fri, 12 Jun 2020 19:58:07 +0800</pubDate>
				<link>https://quire.io/blog/p/how-to-deep-work.html</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">https://quire.io/blog/p/how-to-deep-work.html</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>How to Take a Break When Working Remotely to Increase Productivity?</title>
				
					<dc:creator>Vicky Pham</dc:creator>
				        
				<description>We are obsessed with being “work martyrs” to prove our abilities to meet deadlines and complete the to-do lists every single day. Don&#39;t let your job take away your happiness! Here are some tips for you to take a break when working remotely and still get things done!</description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 27 May 2020 19:58:07 +0800</pubDate>
				<link>https://quire.io/blog/p/how-to-properly-take-a-break.html</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">https://quire.io/blog/p/how-to-properly-take-a-break.html</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>6 Mistakes Project Managers Make that Kill Productivity</title>
				
					<dc:creator>Josh Guilar</dc:creator>
				        
				<description>In this article, Quire looks at 6 mistakes project managers make that kill productivity and what you can do to avoid them.</description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 18 May 2020 19:58:07 +0800</pubDate>
				<link>https://quire.io/blog/p/productivity-mistakes.html</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">https://quire.io/blog/p/productivity-mistakes.html</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>The Art of Being Productive While Staying In</title>
				
					<dc:creator>Vicky Pham</dc:creator>
				        
				<description>As social distancing and self quarantining continue, here are some effective tips to keep you sane during lockdown and still being productive. Being a remote team, we have put together some of the best life hacks for you to enjoy the solitude during this unprecedented time.</description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 05 May 2020 19:58:07 +0800</pubDate>
				<link>https://quire.io/blog/p/productivity-tips-during-lockdown.html</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">https://quire.io/blog/p/productivity-tips-during-lockdown.html</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Wunderlist Alternative: Effortlessly Switch to Quire</title>
				
					<dc:creator>Vicky Pham</dc:creator>
				        
				<description>Effortlessly migrate your tasks, to-do lists, folders, projects from Wunderlist to Quire. Change is frustrating, but we made it easy for you! No more looking for the best Wunderlist alternative. Welcome to a task management software that is here to stay!</description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 29 Apr 2020 19:58:07 +0800</pubDate>
				<link>https://quire.io/blog/p/wunderlist-alternatives.html</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">https://quire.io/blog/p/wunderlist-alternatives.html</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Introducing Quire Mobile 5.0 and Everything You Need to Know</title>
				
					<dc:creator>Vicky Pham</dc:creator>
				        
				<description>We can’t be more excited to introduce you with Quire Mobile 5.0 - a brand new chapter for both Quire iOS and Android users! Faster performance, more user-focused interface, all-new tabbed navigation, dynamic search, new feature Sublist, etc., basically everything gets better with the all-new design Quire Mobile 5.0.</description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 11 Apr 2020 19:58:07 +0800</pubDate>
				<link>https://quire.io/blog/p/introducing-new-mobile-app.html</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">https://quire.io/blog/p/introducing-new-mobile-app.html</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Coronavirus Outbreak: How to Work From Home and Still Stay Productive</title>
				
					<dc:creator>Vicky Pham</dc:creator>
				        
				<description>Social distancing is implemented to slow down the spread of Coronavirus. Don&#39;t freak out if it&#39;s your first work-at-home experience, we will tell you the ultimate guides, from setting up your new office to the way you collaborate with your team from afar.</description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 25 Mar 2020 19:58:07 +0800</pubDate>
				<link>https://quire.io/blog/p/work-from-home-tips.html</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">https://quire.io/blog/p/work-from-home-tips.html</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Quire joins forces with Google and Zoom to offer free accounts for Nonprofits</title>
				
					<dc:creator>Vicky Pham</dc:creator>
				        
				<description>We understand your struggles, and we would like to share the burden with all of the Nonprofits who have been suffering financially amid the coronavirus pandemic. Quire will offer completely free accounts for Nonprofits during the outbreak, no strings attached.</description>
				<pubDate>Fri, 20 Mar 2020 19:58:07 +0800</pubDate>
				<link>https://quire.io/blog/p/coronavirus-nonprofits-free-accounts.html</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">https://quire.io/blog/p/coronavirus-nonprofits-free-accounts.html</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>The Ultimate Guide to Kanban Swimlanes for Better Project Management</title>
				
					<dc:creator>Vicky Pham</dc:creator>
				        
				<description>Kanban board is proven to play a critical role in project management. One of the most important practices of Kanban Board is the Swimlane. This ultimate guide will tell you what Kanban Swimlane is and how to become a Kanban expert.</description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 17 Mar 2020 19:58:07 +0800</pubDate>
				<link>https://quire.io/blog/p/Kanban-board-swimlane.html</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">https://quire.io/blog/p/Kanban-board-swimlane.html</guid>
			</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>
