<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
	<channel>
		<title>Quire &amp; You</title>
		<description>A collaborative task management tool for breaking down goals in hierarchical lists.</description>		
		<link>https://quire.io</link>
		<atom:link href="https://quire.io/blogfeed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		
			<item>
				<title>It is all about time in task management.</title>
				
					<dc:creator>Crystal Chen</dc:creator>
				        
				<description>Time is a tricky thing. We all want to get the most out of it by making the right kind of plan, and doing the right kind of tasks in the right amount of time. But, we often fail. To solve this problem, Quire has got a series of features including start date and time, due date and time, reminders, status, etc. to help you and your team...</description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 21 Nov 2016 19:58:07 +0800</pubDate>
				<link>https://quire.io/blog/p/It-is-all-about-time-in-task-management.html</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">https://quire.io/blog/p/It-is-all-about-time-in-task-management.html</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>How to migrate to Quire? Copy and paste.</title>
				
					<dc:creator>Crystal Chen</dc:creator>
				        
				<description>Many of you have asked about a way to import your work from a different app into Quire, without going through the trouble of entering them one by one. Now, we have the answer: Copy and paste. Be it an Excel sheet with data, a Word document of bullet list, or an email from your coworker, you can easily move them to Quire and continue where you left off...</description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2016 19:58:07 +0800</pubDate>
				<link>https://quire.io/blog/p/How-to-migrate-to-Quire-Copy-and-paste%20copy.html</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">https://quire.io/blog/p/How-to-migrate-to-Quire-Copy-and-paste%20copy.html</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>We’re not Facebook. So why Like?</title>
				
					<dc:creator>Crystal Chen</dc:creator>
				        
				<description>What does Quire and Facebook have in common? Likes. In Quire, we call them favorites. Of course you can ♥ a task and feel proud of the 23 number of ♥ you get, but more importantly, it’s a way to easily see the tasks that matter to you. Personally...</description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 13 Jul 2016 19:58:07 +0800</pubDate>
				<link>https://quire.io/blog/p/We-are-not-Facebook-So-why-Like.html</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">https://quire.io/blog/p/We-are-not-Facebook-So-why-Like.html</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>A photo is worth 1000 words. Your idea worths more!</title>
				
					<dc:creator>Crystal Chen</dc:creator>
				        
				<description>Hey, have you tried the recently-released Quire for iOS? If you haven’t, you’re missing out on a whole new exciting way to jump start your ideas! Too often, we have ideas we want to capture at the very moment, and they may be words, photos or scenes that just pass us by and that we’ll most likely forget at the end of the day...</description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 28 Jun 2016 19:58:07 +0800</pubDate>
				<link>https://quire.io/blog/p/A-photo-is-worth-1000-words-Your-idea-worths-more.html</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">https://quire.io/blog/p/A-photo-is-worth-1000-words-Your-idea-worths-more.html</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Snap your ideas! Introducing Quire for iOS</title>
				
					<dc:creator>Crystal Chen</dc:creator>
				        
				<description>Honestly. How many times have you ditched your ideas? Or, gone through the trouble of drawing them on a napkin or sketching them on a meeting board, and then simply forgetting where to look or losing them completely on the next day, just to name a few? We’re proud to present to you Quire app on iOS - the first-ever task manager that...</description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 14 Jun 2016 19:58:07 +0800</pubDate>
				<link>https://quire.io/blog/p/Snap-your-ideas-Introducing-Quire-for-iOS.html</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">https://quire.io/blog/p/Snap-your-ideas-Introducing-Quire-for-iOS.html</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Type it while you think it, with @, #, &lt;&gt; and more.</title>
				
					<dc:creator>Crystal Chen</dc:creator>
				        
				<description>Today, you’re bound to have a Q-shaped smile on your face, because we’ve got special productivity-boosting tips for everyone, especially those who’re addicted to keeping your hands on the keyboard! Now, you no longer need to switch between keyboard and mouse while adding and prepping your task.</description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 26 Apr 2016 19:58:07 +0800</pubDate>
				<link>https://quire.io/blog/p/Type-it-while-you-think-it.html</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">https://quire.io/blog/p/Type-it-while-you-think-it.html</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>A plan well-laid, a party well-played</title>
				
					<dc:creator>Crystal Chen</dc:creator>
				        
				<description>“Prost!” cheered the Taiwanese girl Laura, the German guy Richard, and a few dozens people as they banged their glasses of beer together while biting down chicken legs, sausages and pig’s trotters in a German after-wedding party in a German restaurant...</description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 15 Mar 2016 19:58:07 +0800</pubDate>
				<link>https://quire.io/blog/p/A-plan-well-laid-a-party-well-played.html</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">https://quire.io/blog/p/A-plan-well-laid-a-party-well-played.html</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Time to Break the Myth of “Multiple Assignees” in Task Management</title>
				
					<dc:creator>Crystal Chen</dc:creator>
				        
				<description>We often get asked, “Can I assign a task to more than one person?” Maybe you have this question too. Now the answer is, “Yes, you can!”. While other task management tools or to-do apps out there say you may be confused as to who’s responsible for what or tasks may be overlooked with multiple assignees, we say otherwise: there are times that you don’t want to bother...</description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 04 Feb 2016 19:58:07 +0800</pubDate>
				<link>https://quire.io/blog/p/Time-to-break-the-myth-of-Multiple-Assignees-in-Task-Management.html</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">https://quire.io/blog/p/Time-to-break-the-myth-of-Multiple-Assignees-in-Task-Management.html</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Turn Your Projects into Customizable Reports in Excel</title>
				
					<dc:creator>Crystal Chen</dc:creator>
				        
				<description>They say old habits die hard. So we get that some of you, or your managers, are used to the flexibility of customizing your own reports in a software application you’re already familiar with: Microsoft Excel or Google Sheets. When it comes to that, you can export your projects into CSV formatted files on Quire.</description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 01 Feb 2016 19:58:07 +0800</pubDate>
				<link>https://quire.io/blog/p/Turn-Your-Projects-into-Customizable-Reports-in-Excel.html</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">https://quire.io/blog/p/Turn-Your-Projects-into-Customizable-Reports-in-Excel.html</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Keep Your New Year&#39;s Resolutions on the Road</title>
				
					<dc:creator>Crystal Chen</dc:creator>
				        
				<description>New year comes with an opportunity for you to become a more productive, better and happier person by kicking off the resolutions you set to accomplish. Having said that, people who set resolutions never expect themselves to follow through. In fact, 25% of them give up by January 7. Here’s a tip to help you go from making them, to actually keeping them.</description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 05 Jan 2016 19:58:07 +0800</pubDate>
				<link>https://quire.io/blog/p/Keep-Your-New-Years-Resolutions-on-the-Road.html</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">https://quire.io/blog/p/Keep-Your-New-Years-Resolutions-on-the-Road.html</guid>
			</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>
